And now,
>> oh, it's starting
>> Wait,
>> yo, act, I'm live.
>> Drake just confirmed he's coming to
Brand Risk.
>> Who?
>> Drake. He's coming to Brand Risk.
>> Are you lying like hell?
>> No. I swear to God,
>> bro. You need to stop lying, man.
>> Bro, I'm on stream. He came my chat and
he said he's coming to support. He's
pulling up to Brand Risk.
>> I'm coming anyway, but Like, you don't
got to tell me. You don't got to lie.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Hold on. No, bro. I
know you're coming, but he's actually
coming.
>> Bro,
>> bro, you late, bro. You late.
>> Wait, how'd you get Bob M and um um
what's the name of the fight?
>> Don't worry about it. We'll talk about
it off stream. I had to work some magic,
you know.
>> Wait, hold on. They got beef though.
>> I got to watch this uh press conference.
But kind of not really crazy beef, but
yeah, Bob been talking a lot about
Johnny and [__] so you know, it's going
to get there. But I got to go. I'm going
to call you after the press. I'm gonna
call you in like 30 minutes.
>> I send you a line. I'm too good.
>> All right. Bye, Chad. Is
>> he
>> chat? You think a
fear
>> post already
watching, huh?
UFC's in the chat.
They're booing him.
>> One of the most dominant forces to the
UFC octagon. He doesn't just opponents,
he them undefeated and dominion.
>> Yo, he's talking already.
Look at Sean. He's like this.
>> Oh [__] Call this man.
>> I got to be in the game.
>> Oh yeah. You [__] [__] you back.
Dope.
>> Hey, go back to the country you fled.
You [__]
>> I'm going to be your daddy in the cage.
I make you cry.
>> Guy the guy leaves his country, flees to
Sweden, goes back home, [__] himself
out to a [__]
>> and wants to talk like a You don't know
what it's like.
>> How do the
>> What's up, everybody? Welcome to the
press conference.
>> Let's go. Who's got the first question?
>> I'd like to start with Hamzat Shamayv.
Hamzad, Sean Strickland has said you you
and he will be enemies until the day you
die.
>> Do you agree? Is this fight incredibly
personal to you?
>> I don't care. It's just one more
chicken. I going to take his head off.
Just squeeze off.
He will be there in two days.
Yesterday you said that Shawn Stricken
was lying about your sparring sessions
and that you beat him in that session.
Can you tell us with Shan here, how did
your sparring sessions go when you
practiced together?
>> I beat him every day, bro. Look at this
man. His dad beat him up every day. [__]
him up and he has some mental problems
and he's crying to speak about that. So
why using him? You believe this [__]
>> What exactly has Sean said that has
offended you the most? Is it the
comments about your country? Is it the
comments about you as a man? What has
offended you about the things Sean
Strickland has said?
>> What?
Nothing. I'm just happy to be here and
smash that guy. Make my money. Be happy.
Go home.
>> Yo, the crowd.
>> Sean Strickland.
>> Holy [__]
>> Sean, obviously you've said a lot of
things about Hamzat. This has been a
very
build up to this fight. But how are you
feeling? Are you overly emotional for
this fight on Saturday or are you calm,
cool, and connected?
>> Look at this face. I'm here now. Look at
this face. Time to pray. Now,
>> let me tell you,
>> let me tell you about this [__]
>> I was there.
>> Walked off the mat when he had co and
retired
>> and his dad Ali had to call him and say,
"Hey, you better get back there and make
me money. I've almost died in a
motorcycle accident.
>> Did I [__] quit? Did I [__] retire?
You let the common cold retire you.
Don't talk about me being a [__] bro.
You had a cough and you quit this [__]
for
Sean. What is more important to you?
Winning that gold belt or beating
Hamzach?
>> You're never going to beat me. Never.
>> Yeah, [__] I beat you in the
gym. I'll beat you here. I'll beat you
on the stage in front of everybody.
every day. Yeah. Shut the [__] up,
little [__]
You got to start calling me. Hey,
I make it right.
>> I've been daddy in the cage.
>> Okay.
>> I've been all day, every day. You,
daddy. You know about it.
>> Relax, bro.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know what your rat came from,
but go back to her.
>> Yo,
>> Dana, question for you. When you look at
the UFC rivalries of the past, where
does this rank in terms of the most
heated rivalries we've had? Top three
all time. Top three all time.
>> Are you going to let them face off at
the end of this press conference?
>> What's that?
>> Are you going to let them face off this
press?
>> Absolutely.
>> Yes.
>> Hey, listen you guys. I didn't come from
a [__] third world. I know how to be a
shut up.
Yeah. Yeah. [__] you. [__] you. Shut the
[__] up. You [__] your daddy. Listen to
your daddy.
Dude,
>> why did he say
>> the therapist? I'm a sociopath. So, why
would I not want to have a face off here
today?
>> Who's got the next question?
>> Quest for the champion, Joshua Van.
Josh, all the way in the back. All the
way in the back right here. Obviously,
as the champion, you want the most
amount of eyeballs for on you when you
fight. What do you make of what's going
on in the main event? And do you think
you could capture some of their f You
got Josh winning or not? Who you you
guys got Josh?
>> Crazy, man. I I'm enjoying every single
one uh every single moment right now.
>> I don't either. So,
>> I don't either.
>> I don't even know your what your
question was, man. Can you repeat it?
>> Just asking, do you think the hype that
the main event is bringing will bring
more eyeballs to you and you could
capture some of those fans with a
performance on Saturday?
>> For sure. For sure, man. It bring a lot
more eyesball and you know, now it's
time for me to show
>> uh what kind of champion I am. And a
lot's been like Josh born when you were
born. Both young guys, both a fighters
fighting for a belt. What do you make of
Tetssuru considering, you know, you were
booked against him before, fell out,
booked again. So, what do you make of
Tatsu?
>> So weird is a great guy, man. You know,
he's a well-rounded guy. Uh, it just
happened to be so he going to fight me
and he about to find out. D
>> similar two questions for Tits Tyra all
the way in the backyard
getting all the attention but do you
think you can steal some of those fans
when you face Joshua Van on Saturday
>> uh chat
>> Rice Gum
>> you guys want to see respect for looking
right.
>> What the [__]
>> I'm I'm glad to see the main event going
hype. Last one for Tatsu. What do you
make of Joshua as a champion? Obviously
weird, bizarre ending in his last fight,
but I think people are very excited
about this fight specifically. What do
you make of him as a champion?
>> Who was that for?
Dana needs an English to English
translator. Yeah.
is uh too short, right? Uh we have to uh
who's the real champion this time?
>> Bro, what does this even mean? The pin
comment.
>> Go ahead. Who's got the next question?
>> Question for Sean Strickland.
>> Sean Hanzat has said all week that all
this security is not for him. It is for
you and your protection.
>> You feel safe up there with him right
now.
>> Let me tell you,
>> I'm an American. I know how to be a [__]
man. And you see how they put my fans
over here? We're We have [__]
We know how to be a [__] man.
>> You see those fuckans over here? You
shouldn't even be allowed in this
country. You guys are the definition of
[__] dog [__] And you need to get the
[__] out of America. Stop ruining it.
You
guys know how to be [__] men. You live
in a country with [__] built by men. You
live in a country built by men better
than you, then you just actively [__]
up. Go call Putin. Have him teach you
how to be [__] again.
>> Yo,
>> and one more for you, Sean. Uh, as far
as the fight itself, Hamza told us
yesterday it's one takedown and it's
good night for you. Do you think you
have some answers that he's not going to
be expecting if this fight goes to the
ground?
>> Yeah, dude. You could try to dry hunt my
leg all you [__] dude, but it ain't
going to [__]
>> Please off your head. Damn the training.
>> Yeah, you coach Eric takes off with from
you. I squeeze off your leg, man. You
was tapping at all the time.
>> Shut the [__]
>> I squeeze all juice out of you, man. You
>> Jews.
>> Oh yeah.
>> Who you talking to? America. America.
America love me, bro. You Nobody loves
you.
>> Oh yeah.
>> All these guys love me. Nobody loves
you. Only your daddy loves you.
>> Let me tell you about this.
>> If he beat you up, I going to beat you
up, too.
>> Let me tell you about this [__]
Why I call
him a cow problem? Listen to your
>> You're making fun. You're making fun a
child.
>> This is why you're a
daddy.
You'll never be a [__]
>> Cry here now.
>> You are a [__]
You are a [__]
>> Yeah. [__] you, [__] Shut up.
>> Yeah, you're a [__] Sit down and shut
up.
>> Hey, don't make soda.
Let him choke you out for a [__] wagon.
[__] you. [__] you.
>> Yo, what the
>> That's what a looks like, guys. [__]
you.
>> This man would stuck off Cordier for a G
Wagon.
>> You should You should cry more.
>> You should cry now. It's not my problem.
You poor [__]
>> I car I need it because I'm rich. You
poor [__]
I would never out like you did.
>> Yo,
>> who's got the next question?
Go ahead. Who's got it? Fire away. My
question is forum.
Yeah, they're doing Muslims.
You got more security standing behind
you than behind Shawn. They think that
they're more worried about your safety
than his.
He's scared. That's why they have to
hold me back.
In Abu Dhabi, you advised the fans of
Robert Whitaker not to wake up and watch
the fight because it's not going to look
good for them. What are you going to
suggest for the fans of Sean Strickland?
My brother in America I have more than
he has ever had. So watch. They're going
to root for me. So it's nothing for them
to see. They're going to love me and
watch me and root for me.
>> Go ahead. Question for Sean Strickland.
Sean, during the buildup of this fight,
you've made a lot of controversial
comments about Hamza Chamay, calling him
things like a cheshin, a ter, and making
jokes about his
>> I am him. I am I got to take off his I
got to kill.
>> My question for Sean. Now, my question
for Sean, now that he's here in front of
you, would you get up and say those
things directly to his face, or is it
all a part of your online persona?
>> Hey, look at his face. He started to cry
now.
>> Listen, I didn't bring religion in this.
He's the one that [__] brought this into
us. And let me tell you, you [__] no
[__]
>> Let me tell you something. If this is
how you act and religion acts all you
[__] out of this country [__] dog.
Let me tell you guys I didn't bring
religion how you do. He [__] did. He
[__] if that is how you
>> let's go bro. Hey
>> America is a nation of Christ. It's a
nation of freedom.
Down now got to sit down.
>> Go ahead.
Question for son.
>> Hey my dog, thank you for your service.
Let's go.
>> W Sean
>> son, do you think your
>> By the way, guys, Sean Strickland is
coming to Branders 14. He told me last
night,
>> you know, man, I think Jama's a bull.
He's always been a [__]
>> Shut the [__] up. I'm sorry,
>> he drives my [__] leg. You ain't
going to [__] bully you. You ain't
going to do [__] bro. I got to put
>> I'm going to send you back to your
daddy. You ain't going to do [__] You
ain't going to do [__]
>> What? Now you talk so much about me. Now
do something. You're going to shoot me a
[__]
>> Hey, and by the way,
>> you want to make SC.
>> By the way,
>> never.
>> you
>> I never said I was going to shoot him,
>> bro. I grew up.
>> We said that he was going to jump me
with him and his little [__] dirty fan
base. We are [__] We stand on business.
We don't do jump. All you do is you
bring these [__] in here and you try to
intimidate me. I will [__] him up and I
will [__] you up. You [__] [__]
>> You should try now.
>> You got another one. Go ahead.
>> And question for Chimayv. Chimayv. Do
you think you will break in the gau?
>> What do you Do you think with your
pressure you will break at the gates?
>> You already break.
>> Thank you.
>> Starting soon cry. You're going to see
that.
>> Thank you all.
>> Go ahead, sir.
>> Dana, a question for you. You often say
that you're not really a big fan of when
things get too heated up at these press
conferences or at these weigh-ins. How
do you feel up there right now?
>> That I say that I don't what what's the
question? You're not often a fan of
these huge heated rivalries and huge
heated press conferences. How do you
feel out there right now,
>> bro? I guessed
>> literally,
>> are you enjoying like you've got a smile
on your face, but do you like this [__]
>> Some some are, some are not. It It is
what it is.
>> And Sean Sean, a question for for you.
Sean, what what have you what are you
gauging from being back in the room with
with Hamzat now? And what did you see
when you were kind of facing off with
him there a little bit earlier? You
know, man, always when you're around
your
he just kind of walks around like a
[__] But the moment you [__]
>> told you I got to bully you.
>> You ain't got to bully you, [__]
>> Yeah, like you surren
I bully you.
>> Yeah. Shut the [__] up.
>> Remember that. Eric. Eric, can you bring
off this guy from me? Yeah. Tell about
that.
>> Let your coach tell about that. You was
always crying in the gym,
>> bro. We were there with you. Tell the
people the weakest people
weakest guy I chose in the gym.
>> Who was weakest in the gym I chose?
>> We were there. The whole gym was there
when this man quit.
>> I've never [__] quit cuz I'm not a [__]
that.
>> Go ahead.
>> John Bernard with KO Sports. This one's
for Sean. Sean Kamzad said this week he
loves you because you're making him so
much money. Do you love him back because
how much he's making you money? He's not
making anything. Take all his money.
He's a poor. He gonna be poor in the
streets in Vegas. You're going to be
>> Let me tell you something, dude. I would
be poor. I'm out.
>> I would in a trailer any day and have
dignity and have to walk a mile in that
[__]
any day. How do you How do you leave a
country? I'm asking you, how do you
leave a country where they they
persecute and murder innocent people and
you flee to Sweden? You're going to work
like you run back when you're going to
be homeless
>> and you yourself out for a G Wagon. So
to answer
you
jealous about that trailer.
>> Wait, what country is he from? Chad has
a Gwagon. I has a 10 G wagon, bro.
>> You got a drive.
>> Question for Hamza. Hamza, no one's made
Shawn Strickland tap out in the UFC. How
much would it make the win more sweeter
if you're the first to submit him?
>> I I submit him many times. He know about
it. The guys know about it. He's not
happy about that's why that's why he's
so stressed. Look at his face, man. Look
at his face, man. He's almost crying.
Cry now. I got to be your daddy.
>> Calm down. Calm down. I'm not gonna be
your daddy.
>> Calm down in the cage.
>> I don't try to shame people. Some shame.
>> Cry about that. And last one. Sean.
Sean, a lot of fans don't want this
fight to play out like DDP verse comes
up. Why will this fight go differently?
>> Well, they don't want to watch a man try
to dry hump you for [__] 25 minutes,
bro. They don't want to watch a boring
ass fight.
>> I don't need
>> I want you to wrestle. I want you to
wrestle. I will out wrestle you. You
[__]
>> I'll wrestle any day of the week, you
mother.
>> Shut up, [__]
>> Anything.
>> Just go be a [__] bro. I know.
>> I hope you're going to show us some men
dance. I'm going to like make you dance
there.
>> Okay. Yeah. Go ahead, brother.
>> Question for Sean. After the fight, will
there be any mutual respect at all or
will you always be at war with
>> Let me tell you about you, Maya.
>> Hey, tell about yourself. What you daddy
did?
>> It doesn't matter.
>> Let's cry now about that.
>> Let's cry about that. Now,
>> this man will
have to look himself in the mirror that
he's a little about you, daddy. I will
[__] die knowing he's
>> the problem because your daddy make you
a girl. Not my problem.
>> Again, you guys see.
>> Hey, in Chia people make the real man.
So,
>> calm down, bro. You're [__] kid. You
c you're a [__] comeback [__]
>> My problem. Your daddy make you a girl
like crying all the time.
>> Let me tell you, dude.
>> Look at his insult, right? What do I
insult? Do I lie? Am I making this up?
This man's a [__] I don't make it.
>> I gotta make you that.
>> Yeah, you're [__]
>> You're gonna be my
>> calm down.
>> Gonna be my
>> You have another one.
>> Question for Dana. Do you have any plans
on returning to the in it dome or was it
like a one type of dome like the sphere?
>> Do you have any any intention to return
to in it dome or was it a one time thing
like the sphere?
>> Yeah. No, we we would definitely go back
there. Yes.
>> To LA.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. Go ahead,
>> Sean. You've had a lot of great fight
weeks, but it this one feels a little
bit different. Are you having the most
fun right now? We see you smirking in
between questions. It seems like this is
the most fun you've had on a UFC press
conference.
>> You guys, I [__] it, man. I love the
fight fans. The energy you guys bring is
amazing. Like, at this point, man, I
fight for you guys. Like, I can't tell
you how much it means to me just to have
support to the fans. like the octagon in
my own life, you know, like through you
guys, man, I've changed my life.
>> I didn't have to [__] up your life. I
got to change your life,
>> but I like I changed my life.
>> Start to cry now. And I can't wait to
go.
>> I got to change your life.
>> You ain't going to do [__] Go [__]
>> You ain't going to do [__]
>> Yeah, I got to change your life.
>> You're going to go back You're going to
go back to suck him off and go get
another Gwagon.
And what was your reaction to Hamza
posting the footage from sparring the
other night on Twitter?
>> Bro, he posted a flow round where I
wasn't even trying. I was still tagging
him. Wasn't even trying, bro. That was a
warm-up round. You still couldn't hit
me.
>> Yeah, warm up round. What's your warm up
round? Because you was crying about it.
Don't hit me hard.
>> And I'll tell you what, I ask Eric when
ask Eric your coach. He knows about it.
After that, after that,
>> your team has the videos about it. Let
them post that. Let them show.
>> Let me finish. Let me finish.
>> He has the cameras inside.
>> Let me finish. Let them show.
>> Let me finish.
>> [__] you. Let them do anything. Not
anything. I got up.
>> We're warming up. Go a little hostage.
>> Why should I see you five rounds in the
cage, you [__] man?
>> I've been all day every day.
>> What happened?
>> I asked.
Hey, tell them when I come out. running
like a little [__]
>> When I ask you, I'll come out from the
from the gym to the street. What did you
say?
>> Tell about that. Tell about that. When I
ask you come out cuz you're power
it, bro. You're just a [__]
>> I tell him I've come out to the streets
and he didn't come out. I went to the
gym. I said, "Come out. We the street."
He said,
>> I sent this a message a couple years
back saying, "Meet me out.
>> Tell about that now."
>> No,
>> tell about that now. You're such a
[__]
>> You were so Hey, you were so scary or
running around.
>> It's like talking to a like talking to a
[__] idiot, bro. This man rewrites
history, bro. We all know
>> can't deal with me now. Yeah, you see me
in real life now. It's not that much. I
far away from Ch. You talking so much
and I do something now. You guys, it is
a true story.
>> Hey, what's true story?
>> It is a true story. He looks
like a true man.
>> And I said, "Hey, meet me at this
location at 5:00. True story guys come
to everyone meet you up there.
>> He said no no sorry it was a
misunderstanding
guys you up every day
>> I would have there
in Vegas allistan cheshna guys beat you
up. You was running from us.
>> You have another question.
>> Running from us you [__] If you ever
hear me say you covered you guys fight
my own battles cuz I'm not come out to
the streets then
>> you are so
do you have any respect for Hamzad's
trash talking
>> no bro I mean again look why you running
from us why you running from us anytime
this man's ever been confronted alone
look at Costa broa made you run away you
little [__] it's on camera hold me back
guysa scared you and made you run away.
>> Hey, you never run away.
>> In two days, you got to see that. Two
days left. Two days.
>> W Sean,
>> I think Sean's going to win.
>> Sean, usually Hamza doesn't say much.
He's very few with his words. Do you
think that you've gotten in his head
this week because he's talking a lot
today?
>> Yeah, he he thought
he know me. He know
you're going to shoot me. Why you run to
other hotels then? Ah because if you're
not coward, why you didn't say same
hotel like me?
>> Wait, what was he saying?
>> Why you didn't say same hotel like me?
Because you come you run from there. I
wait for you in the lobby.
>> Mother, let me tell you something. Let
me tell you something. You little
[__]
>> This is a factual statement.
>> Shut up. Shut up. I told you to meet me
at this location when you were in Vegas
and you said I will quote this is a
misunderstanding. Don't talk about me
running. Shut up.
>> You said that because you didn't have
any little [__] friends.
>> Hey, that's a true story by the way.
>> That's a true story.
>> Is a true story.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, the location is
Newark, New Jersey. Saturday night live
on Paramount. Hey Jersey, you ready for
some faceoffs?
Let's do it.
>> Let's see it. Let's see it. Let's see
it.
Dude,
I know. Literally chat. Tyra and Josh
only got one question.
up
the back, you know. No, no, it's clips,
you know.
Heat. Heat.
Heat
up here.
chat. Who mocks who?
>> How's that?
It's going to be a good This is going to
actually be a good ass fight chat at
flyweight.
>> All right, here we go, guys.
All right, let's get it. Be good, guys.
Be good so we can get a good one here.
>> Yo.
Wait, what happened?
He kicked him.
Yo
yo
>> hungry.
>> You kick his leg. Is there Is there a
better clip?
>> Since I start MMA,
>> bro. I ain't going to lie. He is scary.
>> I always felt I can beat everyone,
>> bro. I won't lie, bro.
>> I know who I am.
>> Go bad. Not
>> I can,
>> bro. Oh, we need a better clip. As a
monster,
>> a force unlike anything the fight game
has ever seen. It's another win for
Hamza. Is a wrecking move,
>> bro. Hamza is scary, chat.
>> Wow.
>> Like I would pressure, pace, power,
amazing wrestling, and he's just a
psychopath. Oh, he chopped. Still
undefeated,
>> bro. Remember when he [__] broke
Whitaker's jaw?
A lot of people is confident before they
see me in real life.
>> Oh, what a shot by Jamaa. Hamza is just
so smothering.
>> Absolutely incredible to watch the
challenger handle the champ in this
manner.
>> I mean, he's just getting mauled.
>> Total domination. Bellto bell.
>> Except they're going to be a champ.
>> Arman Surukin and Aiden Ross had a
$50,000 bet. Arman has $50,000 on you to
win. Does that add extra pressure that
you've got to get this win for Aiden
Ross?
>> Money this little Tik Tok has, dude.
Aiden, know how much money that little
has, bro? He doesn't even little
>> about $50,000. He'll piss on $50,000.
>> Does that put more pressure on you to
get the win for your teammate Arman
Suruki?
>> Do you think the guy who is making
millions, you can push the 50k or get
the pressure on me? That makes sense.
>> Armani, bro, he is scary, bro. Holy
[__] Wait, there's a better clip, bro.
I want to see a better Yeah, like a
closeup. Oh, here it is. Let me see.
Was it bad chat?
>> Let me watch.
>> I ain't going to lie. And he risk
kicking Dana. Well, actually, no. He's
pretty accurate. He's pretty accurate.
Got to get up here. Let's go.
Yo
yo,
>> bro. I'mma be honest, bro.
Look at Dana's reaction. Look. Look,
>> chat. Is Dana happy or upset?
Yo, the crowd is saying goat [__]
>> Yo, y He hit him. He hit him.
Call Armen. All right.
Is he streaming right now?
His leg is [__] bro. I swear to God,
bro. I hope Sean's not injured. There's
no way he's injured, right?
Right.
Is he injured or no?
Fight is off.
Where do you kick him?
It depends where he's kicked.
I don't have Guru's number, bro. Wait,
do I
I'm calling him.
Uh, Guru
chat, does that kick hurt? Yes or no?
>> Welcome to the Oh,
>> nice.
Well, nobody answers me. It's cooked.
>> Started getting noisy. Tables getting
flipped over. Guys running in with and
uh they were screaming get down. I
didn't get down. It was [__] awesome.
D is hilarious, bro. Holy [__]
All right, y'all boys, man. It's time to
get them cookies.